the following content is provided under a Creative Commons license
以下内容是根据Creative Commons授权提供
your support will help MIT OpenCourseWare continue to offer
您的支持将有助于麻省理工学院开放式课程继续报价
high-quality educational resources for free
免费优质教育资源
to make a donation or view additional materials from hundreds of them IT
进行捐赠或查看附加材料由数百人资讯
courses
课程
visit MIT OpenCourseWare at 0 CW
参观麻省理工学院开放式课程在0 CW
that MIT that EDU ha
麻省理工学院的EDU公顷
in
the norm
规范
are
有
the
该
in the last lecture we discussed sinusoidal
在上一讲中我们讨论了正弦
and real in complex exponential signals both
而真正的复指数信号既
for continuous-time and discrete-time no signals will form very
对于连续时间和离散时间没有信号会形成很
important building blocks when we
重要的组成部分，当我们
return to the discussion love Fourier analysis and later lectured
返回讨论爱的傅里叶分析和演讲后
in today's lecture I'd like to introduce
在今天的演讲中，我想介绍
some additional basic signals specifically
一些额外的基本信号明确
the unit step and unit impulse signal let's begin
单位阶跃和单位冲激信号让我们开始吧
with discrete-time and the discrete-time units that
用离散时间和离散时间单位
in unit in polls the discrete-time unit step
在单位调查的离散时间单位阶跃
is a sequence is a indicated here specifically
是一个序列是在这里明确表示，
a sequence which is zero for
一个序列，它是用于零
negative values if its argument and equal to 1
负的值，如果它的参数，并等于1
for positive values up its argument and
对于正值了它的参数和
so mathematically
所以数学
the unit step sequence is one
单位阶跃序列是
for in greater than or equal to 0 and 0
在大于或等于0且0
for and less than zero the unit impulse sequence
对于小于零的单位脉冲序列
likewise is defined in a straightforward way
同样是在一个简单的方法定义
the union Paul sequence is a sequence which
工会保罗序列是序列
is 0 for all values if its argument
是0对于所有的值，如果它的参数
except for an equal 0 so
除了平等0，这样
the unit step in unit impulse sequence are defined in a straightforward way
在单位脉冲序列的单位阶跃以简单的方式定义
mathematically and in fact in they are also related
在数学上和实际上在它们也是相关
to each other in a straightforward way mathematically
彼此以直接的方式在数学上
specifically the unit in paul's
特别是该单位在保罗的
can be related to the unit step
可以与该单元的步骤
through the relationship that i've indicated here
通过我在这里所表示的关系
Beltre van the unit impulse
Beltre面包车的单位脉冲
equal to units that minus the unit stepped away
等于单位减去单元走开
so mathematically the relationship
所以数学的关系
is what is referred to as a first
是什么被称为第一
difference
差异
and to see the validity love this expression
并查看有效期爱这个表达式
we can simply looking at the unit step
我们可以简单地着眼于单位阶跃
and it's the late version so
并且它的后期版本，以便
here we show the unit step you then
在这里我们将展示单位阶跃你再
here we show the unit step delayed
在这里，我们展示单元延迟步
by one so it 0 for and less than or equal to 0
由1因此它为0，且小于或等于0的
and clearly if we subtract that the late step
并明确，如果我们减去了晚一步
from the original unit step everything subtract out except at
从原来的单位阶跃一切都减去了，除了在
an equal 0 which at which point the difference is equal to 1
一个等于0的差值等于1在该点
and so the difference between you have an
所以你们之间的差异有
and you then -1 is simply the unit
然后您-1简直就是单元
impulse sometimes incidently also referred to as the unit sample
冲动有时顺便说一句也被称为单位样本
now
现在
in a similar way we can
以类似的方式，我们可以
express the unit step in terms of the unit impulse and there are several ways
表示在单位脉冲条件的单位工序和有几种方法
of doing this
这样做的
one-way is through a relationship referred to as a running start
单的方法是通过称为运行开始的关系
what I mean by that is
我的意思是
the following expression: if we
下面的表达式：如果我们
think love morning
觉得爱情上午
some from minus infinity
一些从负无穷
up to some bad UN
截至一些不好的联合国
all a unit in paul's
在保罗的所有单位
our unit sample then this running some
我们单位的样品那么这部分运行
in fact is equal to the unit step
实际上等于单位阶跃
and we can see that in a
我们可以看到，在一
fairly straightforward way by simply observing
通过简单的观察相当简单的方式
dead in this expression when and is less than 0
死在这个表达式中，当和小于0
is nothing accumulated in the some
什么是积累了一些
and we can see that graphically as they've shown here
而且我们可以看到，图形，因为他们已经在这里显示
so for and less than zero we accumulate no turns into some
所以对于小于零，我们积累没有轮流到一些
whereas for an greater than
而对于一个大于
0 we cumulate one non-zero value in the some
0我们在一些累积一个非零值
namely the value of the unit sample at an equal 0
单位样本，即在同等值0
so we have then
所以我们有那么
one expression for the relationship between the unit step in the unit sample
一个表达式为单位样品中的单位阶跃之间的关系
we can also develop another relationship
我们还可以发展其他关系
by observing
通过观察
in essence there if we look at the unit step sequence
在本质上有，如果我们看一下单位阶跃序列
as I've returned to hear weekend
因为我已经回到了周末听
in effect think the unit step sequence
实际上认为单位阶跃序列
as a six-session love unit
作为一个六节爱情单元
impulses one following another so
下面再这么冲动1
if we consider
如果我们考虑
forming Assam
形成阿萨姆
all the lady impulses as i indicate mathematically here
所有女士冲动，因为我表明这里的数学
and as i indicate graphically down below
和我表示图形楼下
we have an impulse here at an equal 0
我们有一种冲动在这里平等0
and an impulse here and any calls one
这里的冲动和任何调用之一
and impose here at any cost to et cetera
并处在这里不惜任何代价等等
and when we continue to add these up
而当我们将继续增加这些了
then what they add up to is the
然后他们加起来是什么
unit step sequence and so mathematically then
单位阶跃序列，所以当时的数学
that would correspond to and im polls that an equal 0
将对应于和IM民调是平等0
plus an impulse to 10 equals 1 was an impulse
再加上一个冲动10等于1是一种冲动
at any calls to et cetera now in this
在这等等任何电话现在
in continuous-time we have a very
在连续时间我们有一个非常
more or less similar situation we
或多或少类似的情况，我们
will find it equally useful to talk about a
会发现它同样有用谈
unit step continuous-time signal and
单位阶跃连续时间信号和
the unit impulse continues time signal let's begin
的单位脉冲持续时间的信号，让我们开始
with the continuous-time unit step be
与连续时间单位阶跃是
continuous-time unit step function is graphically
连续时间单位阶跃函数是图形
indicated as I've shown here it's a time function
表示为我在这里表明，它是一个时间函数
which is 0 party less than zero
这是0一方小于零
and it's one for T greater than 0
并且它是一个对于T大于0
and so mathematically what it corresponds to
所以数学上它对应于
is you if he defined as
是你，如果他定义为
a time function which is zero for T less than zero
一个时间函数，它是对于T小于零零
one pretty greater than 0
比0一个漂亮的更大
now an obvious question is what happens
现在一个明显的问题是什么情况
at Evil zero and the difficulty here which is not a difficulty that arises in
在恶零和这里的困难是不是一个困难是产生于
the discrete-time
离散时间
case is that act equal 0
情况是行为等于0
the unit step function is in fact discontinuous
单位阶跃函数实际上是不连续的
which generates a variety mathematical problems
它产生了各种数学问题
and one can define the units that
和一个可以定义单位
at equal zero in a variety ways
在以各种方式等于零
but the essential point is that the unit step function
但重要的一点是单位阶跃函数
is discontinuous so in effect
是不连续的，以便有效
what we need to do is think if the unit step function
我们需要做的是想，如果单位阶跃函数
as the limit all a continuous function
为限制所有的连续函数
and so we can define a function which I specify here
所以我们可以定义我在这里指定的函数
as use a delta see
作为使用增量看
and used to build the T is a time function
并用于构建T是时间的函数
which is 0:40 less than zero
这是0时40分小于零
linearly increases to time Delta
线性增加的时间达
which would correspond to this breakpoint and then
这将符合这个断点，然后
one following that and so
1以下的等
we can think then love the discontinuous units step
我们可以想到那么爱不连续单元的步骤
as the limiting form use a delta at:
作为极限形式使用增量在：
as Delta goes to zero
作为三角洲趋于零
now we also wanted to find a
现在我们也想找个
unit impulse function and it had a fairly straightforward definition
单位冲激函数，它有一个相当简单的定义
in discrete-time in continuous time things get
在离散时间的连续时间得到的东西
slightly more difficult and to motivate the definition
稍微困难和激励的定义
let me return to the discrete-time definition
让我回到了离散时间的定义
all or the rather the discrete-time relationship between
所有或之间的，而离散时间关系
the unit step and the unit impulse function
该单位工序和单位脉冲函数
in discrete-time we saw
在离散时间，我们看到
dead the unit impulse function
死者的单位冲激函数
is the first difference all
是第一个区别所有
the unit step function
单位阶跃函数
well similarly in continuous-time
以及类似地在连续时间
we can talk about and impulse function
我们可以谈论和冲激函数
which is the first derivative love
这是第一个衍生物的爱
a unit step function
一个单位阶跃函数
so the unit impulse as we wanted to find it
所以，我们希望能找到它的单位脉冲
is the derivative of the units that
是单位的衍生物
course we just finished discussing the fact that
当然，我们刚刚完成讨论的事实，
the unit step function is in fact discontinuous it equals 0
单位阶跃函数实际上是不连续的它等于0
but we can't think love its derivative as related
但我们不能认为爱其作为相关衍生工具
to this approximation to the units there
这个近似的单位有
and specifically we will think love
具体我们会觉得爱情
the continuous-time in polls as
连续时间在投票调查中作为
the derivative %uh use a belt 50
衍生％呃用皮带50
as Delta goes to zero so
作为三角洲趋于零，以便
to define the unit in polls we think I've the derivative
在民调中定义的单位，我们认为我已经衍生
love this approximation to the unit step
喜欢这个近似的单位阶跃
and then observe what happens as Delta goes to zero
然后观察会发生什么作为三角洲趋于零
we have then the definition love
我们有那么爱的定义
the unit impulse function
单位冲激函数
more or less formally to find as
或多或少正式地找到，因为
the first derivative of the units step
单位步骤的一阶导
or thought I love as the limiting form
或以为我爱的极限形式
love the derivative love
爱衍生的爱
the approximation to the unit step
近似​​的单位阶跃
in the limit as Delta the
在限额三角洲
the duration love the discontinuity goes to zero
期限爱的不连续性变为零
well let's look at that if we
也让我们来看看，如果我们
think about the derivative love
想想衍生的爱
used to build the T the derivative of course is 0 for T less than zero
用于构建T课程的导数是0对于T小于零
its equal to a constant during this linear slow
其等于一个常数这个线性期间缓慢
and then it 0 pretty greater than Delta so
然后0比三角洲相当大，从而
the derivative abusive Delta 50 will then
衍生辱骂三角洲50然后将
be as i've indicated here and
是因为我已经在这里表示和
is simply a rectangle with a height
简直是一个高度的矩形
which is one over Delta and with which is equal to Delta and observed that no
这是一个比三角洲和与它等于增量，并观察到不
matter what the value of Delta is
不管什么三角洲的值是
the area is always equal to 1
的面积总是等于1
now as we let Delta go to zero
现在我们就让三角洲变为零
what happens is that the width of the rectangle get smaller
什么情况是，该矩形的宽度变小
the height of the rectangle gets bigger the area still remains one
矩形的高度变大的区域仍剩一个
as Delta goes to zero of course the with goes to zero
作为三角洲云当然为零与趋于零
and the height goes to infinity
和高度趋于无穷
and graphically we choose to depict that
并以图形方式我们选择描绘了
as an arrow where
作为一个箭头的地方
the arrow indicates the fact dead we have
箭头指示的事实，死者身上有
and im polls occurring at equal 0 and
和IM民调发生在等于0和